<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
    <title>zencorner blog!!</title>
    <link>https://zencorner.xyz/</link>
    <description>Zen's corner of the internet, home to her silly projects, doodles, and blog</description>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Sunday 31 Dec 2023, 6:53:12 EST</pubDate>
	<title>New Year's Eve!!!</title>
	<description>Holy shit it's already new year's eve???? WHERE HAS TIME GONE?? Hope you all have a safe 2024 :3</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate> Thursday, 28 Dec 2023, 9:55:46 EST</pubDate>
	<title>New shit! Good shit? One can hope.</title>
	<description>Made a new icon for the site updates, lemme know your thoughts on it please :3
	I've also added some more outlinks and some more devices in my about me, thinking of working on sidebar 2.0 stuff in a bit.
	Thank you all for sticking around and watching the site take form <img src="img/heart.png"></img>
	</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Monday, 26 Dec 2023, 11:03:05 EST</pubDate>
	<title>So that never happened lmao</title>
	<description>things have gotten hectic but uhhh yeah hi sorry I keep forgetting to actually do anything I'm incredibly easily distracted and I've just been so very, very tired as of late</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Friday, 15 Dec 2023, 22:13:05 EST</pubDate>
	<title>some additions to the table of stuff I own</title>
	<description>added phones and shit mostly</description>
</item>

<item>
    <category>Site Update</category>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:44:00 CST</pubDate>

    <title>SushiCaptcha v1.2 update!</title>
    <description>SushiCaptcha has been updated with a better image generator, and audio captcha functionality! Also, captchas are now time-sensitive and only valid for one minute.</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Saturday, 11 nov 2023, 4:44:04 EST</pubDate>
	<title>New on-site blog icon</title>
	<description>I call it "Broken Collar," starting small before I start to rebuild bits and pieces</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Saturday, 11 nov 2023, 3:20:21 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Gradual updates</title>
	<description>A bit of expressiveness never hurt, no? add a bit of personality here, complexity there, then throw it across the room until it looks like the most emotionally garbled mess imaginable. then tone it down just enough for it to be legible for other people. expect some changes, fuck if I know how drastic it'll be lmao</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Saturday, 11 nov 2023, 2:39:12 EST</pubDate>
	<title>holy fuck I love this website</title>
	<description>https://astrossoundhell.neocities.org/ LOOK AT IT. LOOK AT IT NOW!!!!! HOLY FUCKING SHIT IT'S BEAUTIFUL!!!!!!!!!!! everything about the fuckin aesthetic is so good and all the rest of the pages on it and all ttnhskese ;;eaef ;aw fioawehrj oiw rhwoi9ar hjfiowrjfedfkl;sdahf;eikfljcfjmsd LOOK AT IT. BECOME ONE WITH IT. IT'S SO PRETTYYYYYYY AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAFKSDL; also all the sites it links to (especially emma's) are just. my mouth is WATERINGGG</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Tuesday, 7 nov 2023, 1:06:43 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Short term memory loss</title>
	<description>I'm super incredibly forgetful could some of you pester me to update my site now and then please</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Monday, 9 oct 2023, 01:44:26 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Housekeeping</title>
	<description>Removed some stuff I don't vibe with and probably made a couple other changes?? I already forgot lol</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Wed, 4 sep 2023, 17:37:21 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Sona stuff refresh</title>
	<description>Redrew all the badges and icons that lacked zenith's current looks :3 (also added music hehe)</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Fri, 29 sep 2023, 14:01:20 EST</pubDate>
	<title>New update wave!</title>
	<description>Added and changed around some stuff to fit my liking woo!
	<ul>
	<li>Added <b>7</b> new splash texts</li>
	<li>Rewrote page names</li>
	<li>Added two new easter eggs</li>
	<li>Added a Super Secret Invitation<sup>TM</sup></li>
	</ul>
	</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Fri, 29 sep 2023, 19:05:11 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Update Addendum </title>
	<description>Forgot to mention I also want to upload a TON of music and the anniversary art piece</description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Fri, 29 sep 2023, 13:16:32 EST</pubDate>
	<title>got busy, updates soon</title>
	<description>Welp, I got really busy and couldn't work on the updates I had planned as quickly. Doesn't matter tho, I've got some time today to do just that! here are some things I have planned:
	<ul>
	<li>New easter egg(s?)</li>
	<li>More music!</li>
	<li>Finally some more art</li>
	<li>More splash text</li>
	<li>Even! More! BUTTONS!!!</li>
	</ul></description>
</item>
<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Tue, 12 sep 2023, 21:12:37 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Anniversary update wave 2</title>
	<description><ul>
	<li>Added new web buttons</li>
	<li>Easier easter egg access</li>
	</ul></description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Tue, 12, sep 2023, 14:59:46 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Monopoly</title>
	<description>The only board game that lets you be a capitalist whore without the slightest hint of guilt </description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Mon, 11 sep 2023, 23:34:12 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Anniversary update wave 1</title>
	<description><ul>
	<li>Added party streamer and decor</li>
	<li>Added anniversary art</li>
	<li>Added more splash text</li>
	<li>Added new easter eggs</li>
	</ul></description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023, 22:31:37 EST</pubDate>
	<title>1 year website anniversary!!!!</title>
	<description>WOOO IT'S BEEN A YEAR!! Thank you for visiting, signing the guest book, giving feedback and ideas, and to all my friends: thank you for all the cool stuff regarding site ideas :3 this whole thing wouldn't at all be possible without my glorious Ashie though, so be sure to give her site lots of attention too!!!</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Fri, 8 Sep 2023, 14:48:23 EST</pubDate>
	<title>Ready Player One is an amazing book</title>
	<description> I just finished reading Ready Player One and holy shit. I loved it so fucking much!! Amazing story, dialogue that actually sounds natural, plenty of "fuck you late stage capitalism" and genuinely the environments are described with so. much. detail. maybe it's just my hyperactive brain making it vivid but it was seriously incredible, I beg of anybody reading this to also read the book lol</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023, 21:48:23 EST</pubDate>
	
	<title>New sidebar art!</title>
	<description> Drew some new sidebar art of my headmate Alpha, styled after Apple's System 6 OS. she'll appear every thursday!!!</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023, 12:15:04 EST</pubDate>

	<title>Incredibly important announcement regarding Icezer/Zeuvia</title>
	<description>PSA! A friend of mine, "Bloops" Had recently departed all forms of social media due to a large incident surrounding a then-friend of ours for two years, Icezer. You can find more information on this here: https://srb2staff.notion.site/Icezer-Zeuvia-and-SuperPhanto-s-bans-ce26b6baafb6416689bef65058e41269?pvs=4 This is a public announcement for you to stand your ground against her to prevent further incidents. Please report any instances of "Icezer" or "Zeuvia" which you may find on discord, she may be found in FNF, Touhou, UTDR or Sonic-related servers. Most importantly, do not fall into her attempts at trying to regain her stance she once had, she'd released a poor response on her twitter regarding the evidence-backed claims made on the main ocument posted. I urge you to stay alert and vigilant towards her and any other groomer situations. </description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Site Update</category>
	<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023, 11:10:30 EST</pubDate>
	
	<title>Better layout and new stuff woo!!!</title>
	<description>art page now has the same galery view that my wifey's has and now there's a separate music page because cramming that much in a single page is gonna be a bad idea in the long run</description>
</item>

<item>
	<category>Blog</category>
	<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 3:40:21 EST</pubDate>

	<title>Minor annoyances</title>
        <description>Woo complaining time because it's nearly 4 am and I still can't sleep despite being too tired to actually really move. what fun.</description>
</item>
	
	<item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2023 0:4:13 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Newsfeed and projects page updates!</title>
        <description>So the newsfeed was broken for a bit because of a freak accident-type bug that literally broke everything but it's fixed now!! That and I added a GalNet card to my projects page, finally a card with a working link. Stay tuned for more updates coming either later today or tomorrow!</description>
    </item>
	
	<item>
		<category>Blog</category>
		<pubDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023 20:27:32 EST</pubDate>
		
		<title>I adore the PSP</title>
		<description>The PSP is genuinely such a cute little handheld console, I myself have a speckled silver PSP model 3008. It's great for playing a bunch of games like Super Stardust Portable, Pop'n Music Portable, Midnight Club 3, MegaMan Powered Up and it's dreaded choppy movement, especially any PS1 game you might have installed, and the DAC and amp in it are so good they're actually less noisy than my PC's onboard audio. I have at least a third of my personal music library (about a hundred or so songs) stored on it and it's great for going out and about and just listening to stuff. Though it can't connect to WPA-2 wifi which kinda sucks but it's not like I use it for anything internet to begin with. you can also play videos and movies on it and installing custom firmware on it is LITERALLY drag and drop. You just- drop the file onto it through usb mode and launch it in the game menu! It's seriously that comically easy!!! It's tiny, pocketable, super comfy to hold, the UMD door makes super satisfying metallic noises, etc. Genuinely my favorite handheld aside from my 3DS. --Zenith</description>
	</item>

	<item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 16:37:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>woo new background</title>
        <description>totally not just minecraft sculk texture lol lmao</description>
    </item>
    
	<item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 2 Jan 2023 19:55:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Weather!</title>
        <description>Weather readout will now change it's icon to display your current weather conditions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Blog</category>
        <pubDate>Sun, 1 Jan 2023 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Happy New Year!!</title>
        <description>Happy new year everybody!!! here's to another year of having fun and being meow even in thr toughest of times &gt;w&lt; --Zenith</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 21:19:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Hitcounter!</title>
        <description>Added a new hitcounter on the sidebar!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 18:13:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Mobile stuff!</title>
        <description>Added new mobile navbar!! Visitors can now scroll the virtual taskbar for easier mobile navigation, and tap the start button to return to the landing page!~</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 21:59:00 EST</pubDate>

        <title>Americano Funky Action!</title>
        <description>Added Sonic Spinball functionality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>New Toys!</title>
        <description>Added the first WIP version of my weather readout!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 17:54:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description>Fixed half the site not embedding properly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Blog</category>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 21:43:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>More.. personal news</title>
        <description>I got covid wOOOOOO        okay for real this fuckin sucks, no idea who brought it home but now everybody in my house has it. honestly though I'm mostly worried about any of my cats getting it. Promise I'll do my best to recover quickly though..! --Zenith</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Blog</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 22:33:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>News Updates!</title>
        <description>Well the past week has certainly been a ride for me but I'm managing, a bit stressed over the practice SAT I have to do this wednesday but hey, not much I can do about it. Stay safe, wish me luck! --Zenith</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 21:27:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>Added Fun stuff page!</li>
            <li>Added more splash texts!</li>
            <li>Added more web buttons!</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:58:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description>Added more splash texts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:44:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>Added visual noise</li>
            <li>Added classic web button to fit on most sites</li>
            <li>Added glow effects to About Me page</li>
            <li>Added tables and more details to About Me page</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:29:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description>Added and finalized the guestbook, including spam and code execution prevention! (CRS and Nano if you somehow find a way past this I swear-)</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 20:44:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site Updates!</title>
        <description>Added my Manjaro partition to the about me page</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Blog</category>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 17:40:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>News Updates!</title>
        <description>Hey everybody, glad to see you all have been following the website's progress! Just want to push an announcement so you know why updates are going to start slowing down. Autumn break is about to end and I'm gonna have to go back to classes for a while, making consistent site updates particularly difficult. Hope you understand, and have a great day! --Zenith</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 17:35:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>Added more to Links+Chats</li>
            <li>Fixed broken link leading to Sonc's site</li>
            <li>Under construction message added to the Art+Music page</li>
            <li>Added better parity between Ash and I's sites (again)</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 17:25:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>Streamlined the newsfeed process</li>
            <li>Added a link to view the raw newsfeed data</li>
            <li>Better scaling and mobile support</li>
            <li>Fixed some formatting issues</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 15:56:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>Added third index art piece for Wednesday</li>
            <li>Added code parity between Ash and I's websites</li>
            <li>Added feed refresh button</li>
            <li>Added different colors and icons for clarity</li>
            <li>Changed image filtering; only vector images have anti-alias</li>
            <li>About Me page finished</li>
            <li>Links+Chats page finished</li>
            <li>site now scales to resolutions higher than 1080i</li>
            <li>Removed Herobrine</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>Site updates!</title>
        <description><ul>
            <li>added more fancy glow and fade effects</li>
            <li>reworked the marquee background</li>
        </ul></description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <category>Site Update</category>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 15:58:00 EDT</pubDate>

        <title>The site is live!!</title>
        <link>https://zencorner.xyz</link>
        <description>Check out what little I have at the start QwQ</description>
    </item>
</channel>

</rss>
